[{"author":"peuimporte","name":"nouveau_deck","description":"une description","index":0,"cardIds":[35,36,39,50],"sizeCardNotRead":4.0,"nextCard":{"name":"carte2","text":"quesetion2\t","answer":"response2","type":"question","author":"azerty","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":36,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"quesetion2\t"},"card":{"name":"carte2","text":"quesetion2\t","answer":"response2","type":"question","author":"azerty","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":36,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"quesetion2\t"},"nbCards":4,"listeCarte":["carte1","carte2","c3","grg"]},{"author":"azerty","name":"olivierDeck","description":"une description","index":0,"cardIds":[40,41,46],"sizeCardNotRead":3.0,"nextCard":{"name":"c2","text":"q2","answer":"r2","type":"question","author":"azerty","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":41,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"q2"},"card":{"name":"c2","text":"q2","answer":"r2","type":"question","author":"azerty","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":41,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"q2"},"nbCards":3,"listeCarte":["c1","c2","c4"]},{"author":"moi","name":"kjhlg","description":"une description","index":0,"cardIds":[53,54],"sizeCardNotRead":2.0,"nextCard":{"name":"bbb","text":"aaa","answer":"aaa","type":"question","author":"Alexis","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":54,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"aaa"},"card":{"name":"bbb","text":"aaa","answer":"aaa","type":"question","author":"Alexis","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":54,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"aaa"},"nbCards":2,"listeCarte":["aaa","bbb"]},{"author":"Alexis","name":"deckAlexis","description":"une description","index":0,"cardIds":[62,63,64,65,66],"sizeCardNotRead":5.0,"nextCard":{"name":"sdf","text":"azd","answer":"sdf","type":"question","author":"Alexis","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":63,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"azd"},"card":{"name":"sdf","text":"azd","answer":"sdf","type":"question","author":"Alexis","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":63,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"azd"},"nbCards":5,"listeCarte":["coucou","sdf","sdffg","xdf","zerr"]},{"author":"moi","name":"Tristan","description":"une description","index":0,"cardIds":[],"sizeCardNotRead":0.0,"nextCard":null,"card":null,"nbCards":0,"listeCarte":[]},{"author":"Amos","name":"amoslist","description":"une description","index":0,"cardIds":[67],"sizeCardNotRead":1.0,"nextCard":null,"card":null,"nbCards":1,"listeCarte":["aaaaaz"]},{"author":"admin","name":"admin","description":"contient toutes les cartes","index":0,"cardIds":[25,28,35,36,37,38,39,40,41,46,48,49,50,52,53,54,56,57,59,60,61,62,63,64,65,66,67],"sizeCardNotRead":27.0,"nextCard":{"name":"carte","text":"rep","answer":"reponse deux","type":"question","author":"moi","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":28,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"rep"},"card":{"name":"carte","text":"rep","answer":"reponse deux","type":"question","author":"moi","succes":0,"fail":0,"user_succes":0,"user_fail":0,"state":0,"id":28,"nbBonnesReponses":0,"nbMoyennesReponses":0,"nbFaussesReponses":0,"question":"rep"},"nbCards":27,"listeCarte":["carte 2 ","carte","carte1","carte2","azerty","azerty2","c3","c1","c2","c4","ds","dsqs","grg","a","aaa","bbb","b","az","asdf","aze","aaaaaa","coucou","sdf","sdffg","xdf","zerr","aaaaaz"]}]